—— 微分享US字幕组 ——
—— www.universesharing.net ——
感谢 笑笑笑 莙。black伟 翻译字幕
你在那里
There you are.
我正要找你
I've been looking for you.
你看到我的另一只鞋了吗？
Have you seen my other shoe?
什么？
What?
你为啥那样看着我啊？
Why are you looking at me like that?
滚蛋
Go potty.
Scotty
Scotty.
得了吧，小子。Scotty
Come on, boy. Scotty.
滚球，Scotty
Go potty, Scotty.
别那样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
啥？
Yes?
这是一天总最好的开始，好吧？
Great way to start the day, right?
我认为我会吐的
I think I'm gonna puke.
妈妈说你下星期走
Mom said you went on a date last week.
怎么走？
How'd it go?
还好。
It was okay.
"Okay" as in you got laid?
Harry
- Harry.
干嘛？
- What?
她听不到你说的话
She can't hear you.
你不是想做爱吗？任何时候
Don't you wanna have sex,
like, ever again in your life?
嗯。我不认为我是约会类型
Yes. I just don't think
that I'm the dating type.
女孩只想跟我上床因为他们在高中看我的书
Girls only wanna sleep with me
because they read my book in high school.
然后？
So?
然后他们就对我不感兴趣了
So they're not interested in me.
他们对我的一些想法感兴趣
They're interested in some idea of me.
那就是为什么你应该在外面工作
That's why you should keep working out.
那样，他们就会想你的肉体
That way, they'll want you for your body.
这种事怎么做？
What does this thing even do?
它会让你变成上帝
It turns you into a god.
坚持
Keep going.
嘿，昨晚我做了一个很糟糕的梦
Hey, I had a weird dream last night.
有一个女孩，她是
There was this girl and she was...
她看起来怎么样？
What'd she look like?
就是一个普通的女孩，只是我梦到的
Just a normal girl. Just a girl I made up.
好，后来怎么啦？
Well, what happened?
她就跟我说话
She just talked to me.
很无聊
That's depressing.
目前，这还是美好的
Actually, it was really nice.
真的？你没有在你的梦里倒下？那...
Seriously? You don't even get laid
in your dreams? That's...
那真悲哀。
That's just sad.
嘿，你的新书进展如何？
Hey, how's the new book coming along?
我不知道。我有一个好的想法，就是为什么我不写一些关于我的爸爸的事呢？
I don't know. I get a good idea,
like why don't I write about my dad?
然后，bam，我开始想这是最愚蠢的事情
And then, bam, I start thinking
that it's the stupidest thing ever.
谁想阅读这“他对我很失望...
Who wants to read about,
"He was disappointed in me...
狗屎，狗屎，狗屎”？
blah, blah, blah, blah"?
对Scotty我感到很矛盾
Also, I'm feeling ambivalent
about Scotty.
嗯，他都流口水了。他一直在追
Yeah, he slobbers. He chews things.
他小便就像女孩子一样，让我很不适应
He pees like a girl,
which makes me feel inadequate.
他需要多出去走走，散散心。这就是我问什么不写书的原因
He needs to go outside a lot, breaks up
my day. That's why I'm not writing.
你认为那是你不写书的原因吗？
Do you think that's why you're not writing?
不，
- No.
为什么认为你不写书？
- Why do think you're not writing?
我现在可以拥有Bobby了吗？
Can I have Bobby now?
你现在需要Bobby吗？
- Do you need Bobby now?
是的
- Yes.
Calvin
Calvin...
你最后一次看到朋友是什么时候？
when's the last time you saw a friend?
Harry。Yesterday
Harry. Yesterday.
不，不
No, no.
除了你兄弟之外
Someone other than your brother.
你给了你其他的病人Bobby吗？
Have you been giving Bobby
to your other patients?
没有，只把Bobby给你
No, Bobby is just for you.
因为闻起来很怪异
- Because he smells weird.
- Calvin
- Calvin...
你决定什么时候去拿Scotty，我们在说什么？
when you were deciding to get Scotty,
what did we talk about?
你说你的愿望是什么？
What did you say your hopes were?
你还记得吗？
Do you remember?
是他帮我约见一些人
That he would help me meet people.
大声一点，行吗？
A little louder, please?
他很棒，我们要带上一些行李徒步旅行
That he would be awesome and
we'd take hikes and stuff.
人们会去亲吻他然后我就可以约见他们了
And people would stop to pet him,
and I would meet them.
但是在人们亲吻Scotty的时候他很害怕
But Scotty gets scared
when people try to pet him.
这让你困扰了?
Does that embarrass you?
没有
- No.
我想给你一个写书的任务
- I wanna give you a writing assignment.
我不会写的
- I can't write.
好吧
- Okay.
这只能你可以做
This would just be for me.
我只要你写一页
I'd like you to write a page...
关于看到Scotty流口水的人和害怕他的人...
about someone who sees Scotty
all slobbery and scared...
还有喜欢他的人
and likes him anyway,
只是这些
just the way he is.
你认为我可以写出来吗？
You think you could do that for me?
不会很糟糕吧？
Can it be bad?
我想会很糟糕
I'd like it to be very bad.
在Calvin19岁的时候我第一次见到他
I first met Calvin
when he was 19 years old.
他当时已经是...
And he'd already been at the top...
纽约时报几个月的销售榜榜首了
Of The New York Times Best Seller
list for several months.
我记得是这样：
And I remember thinking:
他妈的那个小孩是谁啊？
"Who the fuck is this kid?
我怎么才能几时的回去？
And how can I go back in time
and be him?"
一个在下巴长着粉刺的高中辍学者...
A high-school dropout
with acne still on his chin...
让我们知道什么才能变成一本经典的美国小说
gave us what may very well become
a classic American novel.
从那时起，
Since then, of course,
我们都喜欢他的短篇小说...
we've all enjoyed his short stories...
也包括去年的中篇小说“饕餮盛宴”
Including last year's novella,
Breakfast for Dinner.
但只有当我静下心来重读他的作品时
But it was only when I sat down
and reread his novel...
精美的十周年纪念版现已上市
now available in a beautiful
10th anniversary edition...
我才意识到卡尔文·威尔菲尔兹有多么优秀
that, I realized just how good a writer
Calvin Weir-Fields is.
今生有他，实属幸运
We are lucky to have him around.
女士们，先生们，有请卡尔文·威尔菲尔兹女士们，先生们，有请卡尔文·威尔菲尔兹
Ladies and gentlemen,
Calvin Weir-Fields.
- 无与伦比，太棒了
- 谢谢，非常感谢
- Phenomenal, man. Just brilliant.
- Thank you. Thanks.
- 太棒了
- 非常感谢
- Brilliant.
- Thanks so much.
- 卡尔文 - 你好
- Calvin.
- Hi.
你还记得查理去妓院的那一章吗？
You know that chapter
where Charlie goes to the whorehouse?
是不是因为查理母亲的蓝色围裙你才让妓女穿蓝色呢？
Did you dress the whores blue because
it's the color of his mother's apron?
抱歉…
I'm sorry...
你是怎么找到投稿的地方的呢？
How did you know
where to send your manuscript?
我查了查
I looked it up.
那是当然
Oh, of course.
之前你那么成功现在想起来会不会很奇怪呢？
Is it weird for you
that you used to be so successful?
你在这
There's the man.
Cycus，你该提醒我这些事
Cyrus, you gotta remind me
about these things.
兄弟，你得看看我给你发的短信
You have to check your messages,
buddy.
我该穿得正式一些
I would've worn something nicer.
你是天才，没人在意你穿什么
No one cares what you're wearing.
You are a genius.
别说我是天才
Don't use that word.
佩罗塔先生，看这边
Mr. Perrotta, over here.
- Calvin才华横溢
- 看这边
- Calvin always had talent.
- Over here.
但光有才华显然不够
But that, unfortunately, is not enough.
-  兰登，看这边
- 我所做的这一切…
- Langdon, right here!
- All I did, really...
是给他指引了正确的方向，就像是把接力棒交给他
was guide him in the right direction
and like, pass the baton.
Mabel
Mabel.
什么？
What?
我是Mabel
I'm Mabel.
- 我们认识吗？
- 不认识
- Do I know you?
- No, no.
你想要我的电话吗？
Do you want my number?
那是本难得的好书
太棒了
- It's a one-off, that book.
- Great.
- 那是独立乐队的首张专辑
- 谢谢
- It's the first album of an indie band.
- Thank you.
它有着自然的炙热感情……
It has that sort of
unselfconscious verve...
那个…你不会…
that... That you don't...
之后当然会有创作瓶颈，这个…
Then, of course, there's
the second album syndrome, which...
这个我们就不说了
We don't talk about that.
人人都爱这本书，但我们想知道你目前的进度
Everyone loves this book,
but we wanna hear what you're doing now.
重要的是现在，在写什么书，能说说吗？
What matters is right now.
What are you working on? Are you...?
他们爱你，然后抛弃你
They love you, then they throw you away.
- 我是说，如果我要创作角色的话
- 实际上，做普通人
- I mean, if I'm gonna include anybody...
- It's actually easier...
生活更轻松
if you've only ever been mediocre.
如果你已经到达了顶峰
If you've been at the top...
- 嗨，抱歉
-嗨
- Hi. Sorry.
- Hi.
这回杀了你的
It can kill you.
对，Salinger有一个好的想法。他...
Yeah, Salinger had the right idea. He...
写了一个比你轰动的作品，然后消失了，你知道吗？
Write what you can, then, pssh, disappear,
you know?
我没有喝酒
So I've had a drink.
也没有嗑药。我没有...嗑药
But no coke. I didn't... No coke.
我从不嗑药
I didn't do any coke.
Scotty？
Scotty?
对不起我迟到了，Bubby
Sorry I'm late, buddy.
Scotty？
Scotty?
Scotty,他妈的是什么？
Scotty, what the fuck?
她很可爱
She's so cute.
什么？
What?
你的狗。她很可爱
Your dog. She's so cute.
他是公狗
Oh, he's a boy dog.
他只是像母狗那样撒尿
He just peed like a girl.
我们以前见过吗？
Have we met before?
我不认为见过
I don't think so.
你介意我给他画一幅画吗？
Do you mind if I draw him?
但是别太近
But don't get too close.
他有点怕人
He's a little scared of people.
你是艺术家？
- You're an artist?
是的
- Yeah.
我技术超好
- I'm super good.
真的吗？
- Really?
你的狗叫什么？
- What's your dog's name?
Scotty
- Scotty.
你是苏格兰人？
- Are you Scottish?
不是
- No.
我叫他F。Scott Fitzgerald
I named him for F. Scott Fitzgerald.
谁？
- Who?
F. Scott Fitzgerald
- F. Scott Fitzgerald.
那个小说家
The novelist.
很好
Great Gatsby.
我没读过很多小说
I don't read a lot of fiction.
你从来没听过F. Scott Fitzgerald？
You've never heard of
F. Scott Fitzgerald?
为什么？他真的很出名，很重要吗？
Why? Is he really famous and important?
好吧，他大概是现在仅有的最好的小说家了
Well, he's probably one of the greatest
novelists who ever lived.
那很无礼吗？
Isn't that disrespectful?
什么？
What?
在他死后用他的名字来命名你的狗？
这是有点很无礼
Naming your dog after him?
It's a little disrespectful.
不，这是一种姿态
- No, it's a gesture.
对，一种冒犯性的姿态
- Yeah, an aggressive gesture.
想想吧，你是一个小说家
Think about it. You're a novelist.
你认为这个家伙是最好的
You think this guy's the greatest.
所以你你用他的名字来命名你的狗来降低他的声望
So you name your dog after him
to cut him down to size.
这里，你可以拴住他
This way, you can put him on a leash...
嚎叫“坏Scotty"...
and yell "Bad Scotty"...
感到很有优越感因为你在里面撒尿
and feel all superior
because you pee inside.
杀了你的偶像吧，伙计。我完全赞同
Kill your idols, man. I'm all for it.
好吧。Scotty
All right. Scotty.
坚持住
Hang on.
很漂亮嘛
- This is beautiful.
是的
- Yeah.
你的狗或许像母狗那样撒尿
Your dog might pee like a lady,
但是我还是喜欢
but I like him anyway.
嘿，你刚才说什么？
Hey, what did you just say?
我喜欢他撒尿像母狗
I like him just the way he is.
对
Yes.
对，对
Yes. Yes.
像、、、并上他的眼睛
"Pooled into his eyes as though...
像血液一样忽然返回...
Rushed back like blood...
Calvin脸红因为...
Calvin flushed with..."
你是一个天才
You're a genius.
我认为我们不要用那个词
I thought we weren't
gonna use that word.
你是真真正正的天才
You are really, really super fucking smart.
我想它变坏
"I'd like it to be bad."
很高兴你能找到鼓励你的东西
I'm glad you found something
that inspires you.
鼓励我？
Inspires me?
它贬低了我
It overwhelms me.
我逐渐的无法睡觉跟吃东西了
I literally cannot sleep or eat.
我想做的是写作
All I want I do is write.
我的意思是，我今天几乎来不了这里了
I mean, I almost didn't come here today
因为我不想远离她
because I didn't wanna be away from her.
天啦
- Oh, God.
什么？
- What?
上帝啊。
Oh, my God.
我不能大声说出来
Oh, I can't say it out loud.
真是太愚蠢了
- It's too stupid.
当你说愚蠢的事时我爱它
- I love it when you say stupid things.
这真的是非常非常的愚蠢
- Oh, no, this is really profoundly stupid.
好吧
- Okay.
那我创作的这个家伙...
Okay, so the guy I'm writing...
他叫什么？
Yeah, what's his name?
Calvin
Calvin.
我要换一个。
I'm gonna change it.
无论如何，他身上有很多方面复制于我
Anyway, there's a lot of me in him.
我想说的是...
What I'm trying to say is...
就像我去跟她度过写作的时间
it's almost like I'm writing
to spend time with her.
谁？
- Who?
那个女孩
- The girl.
那个我写的女孩。那是...
The one I'm writing. It's...
我在晚上睡觉...
I go to sleep at night...
等待拿回我的打字机所以我可以跟她一起
just waiting to get to my typewriter
so I can be with her.
这就像...
It's like...
就像我跟她恋爱了
It's like I'm falling in love with her.
真精彩
- That's wonderful.
我不可以跟我写的这个女孩相爱
- I can't fall in love with a girl I write.
为什么不可以？
- Why not?
因为她不是真实的
- Because she's not real.
她不是？你确定？
- Isn't she? Are you sure?
不是。我确定
- No. Yes.
她只是我想像出来的产物
She's some motherfucking product
of my imagination!
Lila对我很坏。
- Oh, Lila treated me so badly.
我知道
- I know.
他们的爸爸死后会留下谁？
Who leaves someone after
their father dies?
确实不是爱你的人
Someone who couldn't
love you properly.
一个无情的荡妇
- Someone who is a heartless slut.
够了
- Okay.
好，告诉我她的一些事
- Well, tell me about her.
我以后都不想再说LIla的事了
- I don't wanna talk about Lila anymore.
我指的是小说女主角，跟我聊聊她
Well, I meant this girl that you're writing.
Tell me about her.
Ruby
Ruby.
Ruby sparks
Ruby Sparks.
今年26岁，在俄亥俄州代顿市长大
Twenty-six years old.
Raised in Dayton, Ohio.
- 为什么是Dayton？
- 听来很浪漫
- Why Dayton?
- Sounds romantic.
Ruby的初次心动对象是Humphrey Bogart and John Lennon
Ruby's first crushes were
Humphrey Bogart and John Lennon.
当发现他们其实已经过世时她哭了一天
Cried the day she found out
they were already dead.
高中时Ruby因为和美术老师上床而被开除了
Ruby got kicked out of high school
for sleeping with her art teacher...
西班牙老师也行，我还没想好
or maybe her Spanish teacher.
I haven't decided yet.
Ruby不会开车，也没电脑
Ruby can't drive.
She doesn't own a computer.
她讨厌她的中间名-Tiffany
She hates her middle name,
which is Tiffany.
她一直支持弱者
She always, always roots
for the underdog.
她很复杂，这也是我最喜欢的地方
She's complicated.
That's what I like best about her.
有时候Ruby会很粗心
Ruby's not so good at life sometimes.
她忘记查看账单或兑现发票…
She forgets to open bills
or cash checks and...
她的前男友49岁
Her last boyfriend was 49.
前前男友是个酒鬼
The one before that was an alcoholic.
她预感到生活即将发生变化并且很期待
She can feel a change coming.
She's looking for it.
期待什么？
Looking for what?
新鲜的事物
Something new.
- 感觉很好吧？
- 歇会儿行吗？
- Feels good, right?
- Can we stop a second?
为什么？你还好吧
Why? You all right?
- 嘿，Sue
- 干嘛？
- Hey, Sue.
- Yeah?
没买着辣椒粉，我买了孜然
They didn't have paprika, so I got cumin.
他们是同样的东西，好吧？
They're the same thing, right?
Miles刚睡着，你要把他吵醒了，我就揍你
Miles went down.
If you wake him, I will beat you.
Calvin，你得谢谢我帮你清理烤箱
Calvin? You need to thank me
because I cleaned your oven.
-Susie，谢啦
- 我的女人
- Thank you, Susie.
- Oh, my woman.
够了，你满身臭汗，把你的手拿开
Okay. You're sweaty.
Get your mitts off of me.
-  Susie，你是不是刮…？
- 你都没告诉我你跟别人睡过了啊
- Susie, did you happen to sha...?
- You didn't tell me you were getting laid.
-Harry
- 我只是说说
- Harry.
- I'm just saying.
他说自己忙于创作没时间去我们家
He claims to be writing too much
to haul his ass to our house.
事实是他只是性趣盎然
But turns out,
he's just getting too much poon.
- Harry，我发誓…
- 我没和谁上床
- Harry, I swear to God...
- I'm not getting any poon.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
你跟我说说这谁的啊
- Whose is that?
- You tell me.
我的神啦。Scotty
Oh, my God. Scotty.
- 是Scotty的吗？
- 不，Scotty…
- It's Scotty's?
- No. Scotty...
别让孩子碰那玩意儿，Miles，别…
Don't let the baby touch that.
Miles, don't...
- Susie，孩子喜欢着呢
- 不，他不喜欢
- Suse, he likes it.
- No, he doesn't like it.
- Scotty一直往家拖这些东西
- 看样子他喜欢啊
- Scotty's been dragging them in.
- He seems to love it.
它一直倒腾隔壁怪邻居的垃圾桶
He goes through
my weird neighbor's garbage.
- 这是别人不要了的胸衣吗？
- 是脏的
- So that's a random dirty bra?
- It's dirty.
真恶心，孩子都开始咳嗽了
That's gross. You made him cough.
Calvin，别收了，扔掉
Calvin, don't put it away.
Throw it away.
我发誓，要是你妈知道…
I swear, if your mother knew...
Calvin，这都是什么啊
- 什么？
- Calvin, what is this?
- What's what?
-  没什么
- Harry，过来
- Nothing.
- Harry, get over here.
别翻了
Please, don't.
- 这些是内裤吗？
- 娘的
- Are these panties?
- Fuck off.
我发誓Scotty一直往家里拖这些东西
I swear, Scotty's been dragging them in.
- 对，Scotty是罪魁祸首
- 闭嘴
- Right. Scotty.
- Shut up.
Calvin，把这些扔了
Calvin, throw these away.
Susie,我去看看Harry
- Hey, Susie, I'm gonna check on Harry.
好
- Okay.
- 告诉他一会儿得走了
- 好
- Tell him we have to go soon.
- Okay.
怎么样？
So?
你打算怎么写？
Where do you see this going?
不清楚，这才刚开头
Well, I don't know. I just started.
这是个爱情故事吧
This is a love story, right?
现在谁会看爱情故事呢？
Who reads love stories?
女人
Women.
我告诉你，女人不会看这个
And I'm telling you,
no woman's gonna wanna read this.
为什么？故事很浪漫啊
Why not? It's romantic.
因为性情古怪，生活一团糟还可爱的女人并不存在
Quirky, messy women whose problems
only make them endearing are not real.
完了
Period.
怎么说来着，得“写你所经历过的”
What do they say,
"write what you've been through"?
- 写你了解的东西
- 对，写你了解的东西
- Write what you know.
- Exactly. Write what you know.
- 写你了解的东西
- 对，写你了解的东西
- I've known girls like Ruby.
- Yeah?
谁啊
who?
女孩儿
Girls.
- Lila吗？
- 不是该死的Lila
- Lila?
- Not fucking Lila.
- 你就谈过一次恋爱
- 谈了5年
- You've had one relationship.
- For five years.
你俩都没同居过
You never even lived together.
听我说，Calvin，蜜月顶个屁用
I'm telling you, Calvin,
the honeymoon shit, it doesn't last.
- 我知道
- 和女人生活在一起就不一样了
- I know that.
- Women are different up close.
我爱Susie
I love Susie...
但她是怪人
but she's a weirdo.
有时候，她没缘由地刻薄
Sometimes, she's mean as fuck
for no reason.
她是一个真实的人
She's a person.
你写得不是真人，明白吗？
You haven't written a person, okay?
- 你写的是女孩儿
- 够了，管他呢
- You've written a girl.
- All right, whatever.
作家不会给人看还在创造阶段的书稿
Writers don't show their work
to people at this stage.
我也许不会继续写下去
I might not even finish it.
因为…我不喜欢这么跟人说
Because...
And don't, like, tell people about it.
听着，我没说你不能写下去
Listen. I'm not saying you can't write.
我是说...
I'm saying...
你不了解女人
you don't know jack shit
about women.
瘦杆儿，剩菜剩饭别浪费了
Don't let those leftovers go to waste,
okay, skinny?
明天去健身房吗？
Gym tomorrow?
我要见Cyrus
I'm seeing Cyrus.
星期五呢？
- Maybe Friday?
就星期五
- Friday.
- 我知道
- 小子，还好吧
- I know.
- You okay, bud?
还行
Yes.
这东西滴得到处都是
This thing is dripping everywhere.
你到底打算怎么吃啊？
How are you supposed to eat this thing?
怎么了？
What?
你真不是我菜
You're so not my type.
你不是我的菜是什么意思？
What do you mean I'm not your type?
通常我会找更专断的男人
I usually go for guys
who are a little more assertive.
- 我就那样
- 不
- I'm assertive.
- No.
你是固执，这不一样
You're stubborn. That's different.
我的某个男朋友
I had this one boyfriend...
说我没意思
who told me I wasn't funny...
但其实我幽默感挺好的
but that I have a good sense
of humor...
他讲笑话我都笑
because I laughed at his jokes.
为什么你会跟那种家伙约会？
Why would you date a guy like that?
我年少不懂事。你也肯定有遗憾的事吧
I was young.
You must have things you regret.
不一定
Not really.
一切都会很快回复正常的
Everything's been perfect so far.
所以你和他们约会是因为
So that's what you're looking for
in a guy?
他们够二吗？
Douchiness?
不知道
I don't know.
我想我一直在找你
I guess I was looking for you.
花了我不少时间才终于找到你
It just took me a while to find you.
Ruby
- Ruby.
跳
- Jump!
第一次看到我你怎么想的？
What did you think
the first time you saw me?
我想你是我见过的最漂亮的女孩
I thought you were
the most beautiful girl I ever saw.
当你了解我的时候你不失望吗？
Were you disappointed
when you got to know me?
你怎么可以问这个啊？
How can you ask that?
我很脏乱
I'm such a mess.
我爱你的脏乱
I love your mess.
第一次见到你，我认为
The first time I saw you, I thought:
看那个男的
"Look at that boy.
我将会永远永远的爱他
I'm going to love him
forever and ever and ever."
要是你跟我破裂呢？
- What if you get sick of me?
不会
- I won't.
我保证
I promise.
你好，狗屎
Hello. Shit.
狗屎
Shit.
靠
Hello. Damn it.
好吧
Okay. No.
那好
- Hello.
Cyrus
- Cyrus.
你他妈的在哪啊？
- Where the fuck are you?
对不起
- Sorry.
我在写作，后来我就睡着了
I was writing, I fell asleep.
我立刻就去找你
I'll be right there.
看吧，如果你不说这些，就会没事
Look, if you aren't ready to
talk about this, it's fine.
不，不...不
No... No, no.
我想让你看到我得到了什么
I wanna show you what I have.
我认为接下来你会很兴奋的
I think you're gonna be really excited.
当然，我会感兴趣的。好吧
Of course, I'll be excited. Okay,
这就是我接下来要做的。我退掉我的午餐
here's what I'll do. I'll push my lunch.
没事儿，我现在离开就好了
Okay. All right. Well if I leave now,
我15分钟就到
I should be there in 15 minutes.
好
- All right.
如果不塞车的话
- If there isn't any traffic.
天啊。Scotty
Oh, damn it. Scotty.
怎么了？
- What?
没事，我的狗撒尿了
- Nothing. My dog has to pee.
我把它放到后花园
- I'll put him in the backyard.
我会带它出去
- I'll take him out.
好，谢谢
- Great. Thank you.
Cal？
- Cal?
Cal?
你好？
Hello?
我昨晚在床上还想起你
I missed you in bed last night.
你现在写了好作品吗
- Did you get some good writing done?
你在哪里吗？
- Are you there?
上帝啊
- Oh, God.
你想被咬吗？
- Hey, you want a bite?
爽快
- It's Crispix.
我认为我已经忘记他了
- I think I lost him.
天啊，发生了
God, it's happening.
这个时候终于发生了
It's really happening this time.
他们让我住院了
- They're gonna hospitalize me.
怎么回事？
- What's wrong?
他们都认为我很聪明
They all thought I was so smart,
但是原来是神经失常
but it turns out I was just batshit.
Calvin?
- Calvin?
他妈的什么事啊？
- What the fuck?
Calvin
Calvin.
这不是真的，这不是真的
It's not real. It's not real.
这不是真的
It's not real.
好吧，你这是在做梦
Okay, you're dreaming.
你这是在做梦
You're dreaming.
你这是在做梦。。。
You're dreaming...
你马上就会醒过来...
and you're going to wake up...
立刻
right now.
靠
Oh, shit.
Calvin？你对我发火？
Calvin? Are you mad at me?
天啦，这不是真的
Oh, God. It's not real.
这不是真的，这不是真的
It's not real. It's not real.
这不是真的
It's not real.
医生
Doctor...
你好，Rosenthal医生。这是Calvin Weir-Fields
Hi, Dr. Rosenthal. It's Calvin Weir-Fields.
有些事将要发生
Something has come up...
如果你尽可能的找我，我会很欣慰的。谢谢
and I'd appreciate it if you called me
as soon as possible. Thank you.
Ruby？
嘿
- Ruby?
- Hey.
我知道你可能会饥饿
I thought you might be hungry,
所以我拿些鸡蛋给你
so I'm making you some eggs.
怎么回事？
- What's wrong?
没事
- Oh, nothing.
Nothing.
是这些吗，或许，你的？
Are these, by any chance, yours?
当然，，他们是我的
Yeah, of course, they are.
他们还属于谁？
Who else would they belong to?
天啦
Oh, my God.
你还看到有其他人？
- Are you seeing someone else?
没有
- Oh, no.
不，不，我没有...
No, no, no, I'm not...
我没有其他人除了你
I'm not seeing anyone other than you.
你会道歉吗？
Will you excuse me?
还记得爸爸过去说我有活跃的想象力吗？
Remember how Dad used
to say I had an overactive imagination?
你是说Ruby在你那里？
Are you saying Ruby is in your house?
今天早上我才见到她
I started seeing her this morning.
就像那部电影Harvey，除非她不是巨兔
It's like that movie Harvey,
except she's not a giant rabbit.
这也不想她想象出来的
It's not like she knows
she's imaginary, either.
她认为在书中我们是有关联的
She thinks we're in the relationship
in my book.
这把我吓到了
It is freaking me out.
我在会议的中间
- I'm in the middle of a meeting.
但是这是一件不可预见的事
- But this is an emergency.
我可能不能自制
I may be losing my mind.
等我一小会，就一小会...
- Just give me one sec. Just...
Harry，Harry。
- Harry. Harry.
Ruby是不可能在你家里的
There's no possible way
that Ruby's in your house...
因为她不是真实的
because she's not a real person.
我知道她不是真实的，但是我跟你说
I know objectively she is not real,
but I'm telling you...
我可以看到她，我可以嗅到她的气息
I can see her, I can smell her.
当她摸我的时候，我可以感觉到
When she touched me, I could feel it.
她在厨房里煎鸡蛋，真的鸡蛋
She's making eggs in my kitchen.
Actual eggs.
很好
That's great.
Calvin，我在工作。我在一个很重要的会议的中间位置
Calvin, I am at work. I'm
in the middle of a very important meeting.
我没办法立刻处理你的破事。
I cannot deal with your shit right now.
听我说，我要你离开你的房子
Listen to me.
I want you to leave the house...
去见见朋友。去见你那不会明白你的想象力的朋友
see a friend. A friend
who can't see your imaginary friend.
如果今晚还没解决，我们再聊，好吗？
If this is still an issue tonight,
we'll talk, okay?
好吧。我打电话给我的朋友
Okay. I'll phone a friend.
我很抱歉，我只是...
Sorry about that, I was...
这个周末，Kobe开一个烧烤晚会。你有什么计划吗？
Kobe's having a barbecue this weekend.
You got plans this weekend?
是Calvin
It's Calvin.
我姓Weir-Fields，中学时
Weir-Fields. From high school.
一名作者
Yeah, the writer.
在西班牙语言课上我做你旁边
I sat next to you in Spanish class.
不好意思，我要走了
Actually, I gotta go.
你们去哪？
Where are you going?
外面
- Out.
哪里？
- Where?
去超市
To the store.
为啥？
What for?
购买一些食材
To get some stuff.
我可以一起吗？
- Can I come?
不行
- No.
为什么？
- Why not?
因为.
- Because.
求求你了？
- Please?
不行
- No.
求求你了？
Please?
点九KCRW
Point-nine KCRW.
上一个，给KCRW人员的票
Up next, tickets for KCRW members.
如果在最后90天内你没有从我们这得到任何东西
If you haven't won anything from us
in the last 90 days...
我听说他们要在墓地那里办一个僵尸电影节
I hear they're doing a zombie film festival
at the cemetery.
你想去吗？一有人被咬就可以用射击哦
You wanna go? We could do a shot
every time someone gets bitten.
好吧。拜
Okay. Bye.
拜？你要去哪?
Bye? Where are you going?
不去哪啊
Nowhere.
Café Figaro。我又朋友在那，不会很久的
Café Figaro. I've got this friend.
It won't take long.
我应该做什么？
What am I supposed to do?
留在这。享受购物
Stay here. Enjoy the shops.
我很快回来
I'll be back soon.
当我没有马上接你的电话的时候
When I didn't hear from you right away...
我还以为你把我的号码弄丢了
I figured you had lost my number
or something.
至少我的室友这么认为
At least that's what my roommate said
must have happened.
不，我没有忘记你的号码。实际上我遇见你的那晚
Oh, no, I didn't lose your number.
Actually the night I met you...
我开始写作了，花了我不少时间
I started writing something,
so my life's been really consuming.
你遇见我的那晚？
The night you met me?
是不是我？
Am I...?
没什么.没什么。
Never mind. Never mind.
我是你的作品里的人物吗？
Am I in it?
- 现在不能说
- 当然
- I can't really talk about it.
- Right, of course.
如果你写了我，小说出版发售的时候
But if I am, like, when it comes out
in stores and stuff...
- 你会跟我说那个角色是我吗？
- 我没写你
- ...will you tell me which character I am?
- You're not in it.
我知道，但如果写了呢？
Right, but if I am?
我会告诉你
I will let you know.
好的，太好了，太好了
Okay. Awesome. Awesome.
你经常这么干吗?
So do you do this a lot?
- 干什么？
- 午间约炮
- Do what?
- Meet up in the middle of the day for sex.
不，不，我只想找人说会儿话
No. No, that's not...
I just wanted someone to talk to.
这样啊
Right. Right.
男人永远不会只想和女人说说话
Well, men never just wanna talk
to women.
我就是这样 -
如果你坚持的话
- I do.
- If you say so.
你成年了吗？
Are you even legal?
还没到合法饮酒的年纪，但
I mean, not to drink, but, yeah.
当然，你想…
Of course. Do you...?
你想去别的地方吗？
Do you wanna go someplace?
- 嗨
- 抱歉，什么？
- Hi.
- Sorry, what?
你想去我那儿吗？
Do you wanna go to my place?
你好
对不起
- Hi.
- Sorry.
我很抱歉
发生了什么
- I'm sorry.
- What's going on?
我要暂停吗
我想我听到了一些声音
- Am I interrupting?
- I thought I heard something.
你想离开这里？
Calvin
- Do you wanna get out of here?
- Calvin.
你知道这个女孩吗
是的，你好，我是Ruby,Calvin的女朋友
- Do you know this girl?
- Yeah. Hi, I'm Ruby, Calvin's girlfriend.
我想我们以前没见过
I don't think we've met.
不是
No.
我是Mable，我要走了
I'm Mabel. I was just going.
你可以看到她？
是，我可以看到他
- You can see her?
- Yeah, she can see me.
我可以看到她
I can see her.
你可以看到他
不要误会，好吗
- You can see her.
- Let's not make this worse, all right?
对不起，我不知道
你可以快点来吗
- Sorry, I didn't know.
- Did Harry put you up to this?
什么，你的哥哥不在吗
什么
- What, your brother is in on this?
- What?
Rudy，很高兴见到你
calvin,好好写
Ruby, it was very nice meeting you.
Calvin, have fun writing.
那女的他妈是谁？
Who the fuck was that?
你可以看到她吗
Calvin,那是谁
- Can you see her?
- Calvin, who was that?
我可以看她吗
他可以看到我吗，你是，，，？停
- Can I see her?
- Can he see me? What are you...? Stop.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you, man?
她没事
She's real.
哦，不，Ruby
Oh, no. Ruby!
Ruby!Ruby!
Ruby! Ruby.
离我远点
Ruby!Ruby!
- Get away from me!
- Ruby! Ruby!
走开，走开
Ruby!
- Get away! Get away!
- Ruby!
Ruby!求你了，听我说的
走
- Ruby, please, listen to me.
- Let go!
停
听我说，冷静点，Ruby!
- Stop!
- Listen to me. Calm down. Ruby.
不要靠近我
喂，你还好吧
- Get away from me!
- Hey, you okay?
你想让我叫警察来吗？
You want me to call the police?
不用，谢谢
他是个完全的混蛋
No. Thank you.
He's just being a complete asshole.
你确定？
Are you sure?
是的
Yeah.
谢谢，我很好
Thank you, I'm fine.
他是个完全的混蛋
你站远点
- Ruby.
- You stay away.
天啊，我应该知道的
你一直表现得很奇怪，住手
God, I should have known. You've been
acting like such a freak... Stop!
放开我
Let go of me!
放我下来
Put me down!
放我下来，要不然我要叫了
Put me down or I'm gonna scream!
Ruby.
停下
- Ruby.
- Stop it!
放我下来
Ruby？
- Put me down!
- Ruby?
噢，天啊，停下来
Oh, my God, stop!
停下来，噢，别咬了，
别咬了
Stop it. Oh, do not bite.
Do not bite.
听我说
Listen to me.
事情发展太快
，我解释不清楚
There is a lot that is new here,
more than I can tell you.
我无法接受这一切，你懂吗？
I'm having trouble processing it all,
okay?
告诉我关于这件事
Then talk to me about it.
不要跟其他女孩约会
Don't go on a date with another girl.
我没有约会
I wasn't on a date.
你怎么了
我不知道，抱歉
- What is going on with you?
- I don't know. I'm sorry.
哦，我只是有点麻烦
Oh, I'm just having trouble...
无法正常处理眼前的情况
wrapping my head
around the reality of this situation.
你在这里
That you're here.
你是真实的
That you're real.
这一切太不可思议了
It all seems pretty incredible.
什么
What?
亲我，笨蛋
Kiss me, stupid.
他妈的
Holy shit.
看，我知道难以置信
但是你不得不相信我
Look, I know it's a lot to take in,
but you have to believe me.
他是真实的
She's real.
我不知道为什么会这样
I don't know how or why...
但是她在这里而且她是真实的
but she's here and she's real.
我很喜欢
And I like it.
“真实”对于其他人意味着可以看到她
那就是我要告诉你的
- "Real" as in other people can see her.
- That's what I'm trying to tell you.
我们去了餐厅
带史考特去公园遛弯儿
We've been to restaurants.
We take Scotty for walks in the park.
有人跟她说话，她很和善
那不可能
- People talk to her. She's very friendly.
- That's impossible.
显然有可能
It's apparently not.
Rosenthal先生怎么说
What does Dr. Rosenthal say?
你他妈的认真的吗？
Are you fucking serious?
出现幻觉了人们会去看心理医生
People have shrinks
for when they start seeing things.
我看不见东西
I'm not seeing things.
- Calvin，打电话给他
不
- Calvin, call him.
- I can't.
我告诉他如果我跟他说露比是我虚构的角色，
他不会相信
I told him when she was a character.
He won't understand.
打电话给他要不让我告诉妈
他会认为我有病
- Call him or I'm telling Mom.
- He'll think I'm crazy.
你可能就是有病
You might be crazy.
状况失控了
The situation is crazy.
我不是
I am not.
你听到...?嘿
Do you hear...? Hi.
你听到你自己的声音吗，有吗
你听到你自己的声音吗，
Do you hear yourself? Do you?
Do you hear yourself? Really?
跟一个你虚构的女孩同床共枕绝对不可能
There's no way that you're sleeping
with a girl that you made up.
所以她不知道我写的是她
Hey, so she doesn't know
that I wrote her...
所以不要说任何关于底稿的事情，好吗
so don't say anything
about the manuscript, okay?
好吧
Yeah, okay.
Hi, Ruby，很高兴见到你
我们现在打电话给意思？
Hi, Ruby. Great to meet you.
Can we call the doctor now?
- Harry.
- Calvin!
你好
Hey.
你怎么来这么晚
What took you so long?
你好， Ruby,这是我的哥哥，Harry.
你好
- Hey, Ruby, this is my brother, Harry.
- Hey.
Harry.你好
你好
- Harry. Hi.
- Hi.
你好，很高兴见到你
你好
- Hi. It's great to meet you.
- Hi.
我之前听过很多关于的事情
从Calvin那里
I've heard so much about you
from Calvin.
你是Ruby
You're Ruby.
你是Harry
You're Harry.
来自俄亥俄代顿的画家
The painter from Dayton, Ohio.
是的
- Yep.
留下来吃晚饭吗？
我在做肉糜糕
Are you staying for supper?
I'm making meat loaf.
她的厨艺很好
She's an amazing cook.
是的，我可以跟你聊一会吗
去外面？
Yeah. Can I talk to you a second?
Outside?
好的
Okay.
你做什么了？从克雷格信息网雇了个演员吗
？这不好玩
What did you do? Hire some actress?
Craigslist? This isn't funny.
我告诉过你，她只是消失了
I told you, she just appeared.
你是个作家，不是Ricky Jay
我知道
- You're a writer, not Ricky Jay.
- I know that.
肯定得有合乎逻辑的解释
爱是没有逻辑的
- There's gotta be some logical explanation.
- Love isn't logical.
不，但是你知道爱是什么吗
物理学或者玄学
No, but you know what is?
Physics. Or metaphysics.
不会有人凭空出现
她是
- People don't appear out of thin air.
- She did.
怎样
我不知道
- How?
- I don't know how.
这是爱，这是想象
It's love. It's magic.
好的
你在做什么
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
打电话给你的医生
不要打
- Calling your doctor.
- Don't.
Harry. Harry.
给我
- Harry. Harry.
- Give me that.
我们可能...给我电话
Harry. 请听我说
- We might... Give me the phone.
- Harry, listen to me, please.
记得你说过什么吗
当你遇见Susie的时候
Remember what you told me
when you met Susie?
我没有假装她是我创造的
你说她是你梦想中的女孩
- I certainly didn't pretend I invented her.
- You said that she was your dream girl.
那是我的事
That's what happened to me.
Harry，不要嘲笑我
Harry, don't laugh at me.
你就没想过她可能是个骗子吗
Has it occurred to you
that she might be an imposter?
一些女孩想要靠近你
设法去拿到你写的东西
Some girl wanted to get close to you,
somehow got her hands on what you wrote.
你是唯一一个读了我的稿子
You're the only one
who's read my manuscript.
所以你开了一个玩笑
好的，好的，好的
- So unless you're playing some joke...
- Okay, okay, okay.
说说你创造的这个人
你写的任何东西关于她是真实的
Let's say you created this person.
Everything you wrote about her came true.
即使是最微妙的小事
是的
- Even the smallest things?
- Yes.
你试着写更多吗
没有
- Have you tried writing more?
- No.
写些关于她的事情
Write something about her.
为什么，她很完美
Why? She's perfect.
写些关于她的事情
看看这是否会变成现实
Write something about her,
see if it comes true.
如果没有，那么你是对的
这是他妈的完美
If it does, then you're right
and this is a fucking miracle.
如果什么都没有发生
And if nothing happens...
可能我们要去警察局了
maybe we go to the police.
不要打电话
去那里，正常活动，走
- Don't call...
- Just go in there and act normal. Go up.
你的行为要正常
我不是说...
- You act normal.
- I'm not gonna say...
我们上楼去
上网查查
We're gonna go upstairs
and check on something online.
你俩、们在外面嗑药了吗？
Were you guys getting stoned out there?
好的，这是那时我离开的地方
Okay, here's where I left off.
写些我们马上能察觉的东西
It has to be something
we notice right away, okay?
一些东西
Something obvious.
她穿的是什么
是
- What she's wearing?
- Yes. Yes.
她穿的是什么
What she's wearing.
What was she wearing?
粉红色的
Was it pink?
我知道了
I got it.
好的，好的
Okay. Okay.
写些她说的流利的法语
Write that she speaks fluent in French.
好，写下它
Yeah, just put it down.
我正在写
我..
- I'll do it.
- I...
哈
Bah!
我等会就回来，我有些事要做
等下，拿着
- I'll be right back. I have to do something.
- No, wait, hold it.
Calvin
一瓶酒
Bottle of vino.
好，你的哥哥看起来
很能喝
Great. Your brother looks like
he could use a drink.
我不得不说
那是我吃过的最好吃的肉
I have to say,
that's the best meat loaf I've ever had.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是家传菜谱
It's a family recipe.
我真的没有拿卡
I can't really take credit.
所以你的，你的家在俄亥俄州
So your... Your family's in Ohio?
是的，实际上，我的父母
在我还很小的时候死于车祸
Yeah. Actually, my parents died
when I was a baby in an accident...
我离开了那里
and I got moved around a lot.
我想不会再搬了
I guess the habit stuck.
我在六年时间去了9个城市，所以
9个?
- I've lived in nine cities in six years, so...
- Nine?
是的
很多城市
- Yeah.
- That's a lot of cities.
很抱歉，我一直没认真对待这次谈话
I'm so sorry. I'm totally
monopolizing this conversation.
不，很奇妙
No. This is fascinating.
请一直往前走
Please, keep going. Please.
多么好的一个男孩
What nice boys.
你的妈妈一定很自豪
在10年很难做到这样
Your mom must be so proud.
It's hard to raise a decent guy.
我想一个人肯定要做些疯狂的事情
Oh, I think a person would have to do
something pretty amazing...
去塑造一个好女性
to produce a good woman.
很好
Okay. Great.
你们看起来很像对方
我想Harry要走了
You guys like each other.
I think Harry has to go now.
是的，兄弟
Right, buddy?
他有时是个控制狂，对吧？
He can be such a control freak, right?
我会很快回来
晚安
- I'll be right back.
- Good night.
我希望我们能快点见面
嘿，所以？
- See you soon, I hope.
- Hey. So?
上车
什么
- Get in the car.
- What?
上车
为什么？什么？
- Get in the car.
- Why? What...?
太疯狂了！
That was insane!
- Harry..
这太疯狂了
- Harry...
- This is insane.
你用想象力造出了一个女人
You manifested a woman with your mind.
老妈会被吓得
你不能告诉妈妈
- Mom's gonna fucking freak.
- You can't tell Mom.
为什么？她很喜欢所有这个年龄的女孩
认真的
- Why not? She loves all this New Age shit.
- Seriously...
你不能告诉任何人
妈妈，Susie，任何人
you can't tell anybody.
Not Mom, not Susie. No one.
这太疯狂了，我怎么能不告诉别人
他们会认为她是怪胎
- This is amazing. How can I not tell?
- They'll think she's a freak.
我们可以说她是你的女朋友
她是我的女朋友
- We're gonna pretend she's your girlfriend?
- She is my girlfriend.
认真的？
Seriously?
为什么不
你的女朋友
- Why not?
- Your girlfriend.
怪事发生了
我不这么认为
- Stranger things have happened.
- I don't think so.
我想这是最奇怪的事
I think this is pretty much the strangest
thing that's ever happened, ever.
你要跟她结婚？
跟她生小孩？
You gonna marry her?
Have kids with her?
我不知道
但是那不是像乱伦了吗？
- I don't know.
- But wouldn't that be like incest?
或者意念
我不关系
- Or mind-cest?
- I don't care.
我爱她
I love her.
不要摧毁
Please, don't ruin this for me.
答应我，不告诉任何人
Promise me, no one.
好
Fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿，你可以的，像改变她
Oh, hey, so you can, like, change her.
我想
I guess.
你可以，像特殊的东西
如果你想
You could, like, tweak things
if you wanted.
特殊？你的意思是什么
Tweak? What do you mean?
我不知道，像任何东西
大胸，长腿
I don't know, like anything.
Big tits, long legs...
我喜欢她的细腿
知道我多少次我想装个按钮吗
- I like her little legs.
- Know how many times I wanted a button...
摁完她就不做那些烦人的事了
to make Susie stop doing
all the annoying shit she does?
我意思是你可以做工作
任何你想的时候
I mean, you could get blow jobs
whenever you wanted.
Ruby喜欢
Ruby loves giving blow jobs.
现在，还是几月几天
Now, but what about
in a couple months or days?
女人让男人琢磨不透
现在我看着苏西还会问自己
Women are mysterious creatures.
I still look at Susie like:
你是谁，你是谁
"Who are you? Who are you?"
我知道Ruby, Harry. 我写过她
I know Ruby, Harry. I wrote her.
所以你可以让任何事
So you can make her, like, do anything.
对于男人任何地方
For men everywhere...
告诉我你不会让那浪费
tell me you're not gonna let that
go to waste.
我不会再写关于她的故事了
I will never write about her again.
Calvin?
嘿
Hey.
所以他喜欢我？
So did he like me?
他爱你
He loved you.
停，停，停
Stop, stop, stop.
你好，如果是我妈妈，请，不要..
Hey, if it's my mom, please, don't...
喂
Hello?
有人吗，有人在吗，我不是,,
Hello, is anyone there? I don't...
嘿，妈
Hi, Mom.
噢，甜心，嘿
我不确定你在那里
Oh, hi, sweetie. Hi.
I wasn't sure you were there.
你想做什么，老妈
What do you want, Mom?
我想知道你这个周末
你回来吗
I was wondering if
you're gonna make it up this weekend.
我跟你说过我们不回去
我们很忙
I told you we can't this weekend.
We're busy.
哦，跟谁
跟谁做事？
- Oh, with what?
- Busy with what?
你的哥哥说
你没有写作了
Your brother says
you haven't been writing.
他不知道
你已经跟这个女孩一起几个月了
- He doesn't know.
- You've been with this girl for months.
我还没有见过她
我开始想她是不是不存在
I haven't even met her.
I'm beginning to think she doesn't exist.
什么，不，我意思是，是的
What? No. I mean, yes.
所以我可以什么时候见到她
很快
- So when can I meet her?
- Soon.
下星期？
Harry和Susie也会在
Next weekend?
Harry and Susie will be here.
请进
Come on, please?
看，我们有个计划
Look, we have plans.
我会打给你的，好吗
我正在开车
I'm gonna call you later, okay?
I'm driving.
我们为什么不能去大索尔
Why can't we go to Big Sur?
恩，我们必须要找人照顾Scotty
Well, we'd have to find someone
to watch Scotty.
我们可以带着他跟我们一起
We could take him with us.
我不知道，Mort
I don't know. Mort...
他们的房子很怪异
Their house is weird.
你不想让我跟你妈妈见面
You don't want me to meet your mom.
当然，我想让你跟我妈妈见面
Of course, I want you to meet my mom.
我会邀请她来参加圣诞节，好吗
I'll invite her down for Christmas, okay?
嘿，你知道在维尔街有间咖啡店吗
一间新开的？
Hey, you know that coffee shop on Dwyer?
The new one?
是的
Yes.
我在想可能
我会试着去找份工作
I was thinking maybe
I could try to get a job there.
好，我跟你说
我很支持你去画画
Well, I told you,
I'm happy to support you while you paint.
亲爱的，我有点累了
Honey, I'm sort of tired.
好的
Okay.
关灯吧
Let's turn out the light, then.
只是，可能如果我不在周围
你可以写更多的东西
It's just, maybe if I wasn't around,
you could get more writing done.
你没有做事吗当我们第一遇见的时候
Weren't you working on something
when we first met?
Calvin?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
收拾东西去大索尔
Just packing for Big Sur.
真的？
Really?
是的
Yeah.
看看这个地方
Look at this place.
当然，这里
All right, this is it.
你问这个
You asked for it.
你不担心任何事
You have nothing to worry about.
看，为什么今晚
我们不呆在别的地方呢
Look, why don't we stay
somewhere else tonight?
只有你和我，有上千个旅馆
Just you and me. There's a thousand
bed-and-breakfasts around.
亲爱的，很好
会很浪漫
- Honey, it's gonna be great.
- It could be romantic.
最后
你好
- Finally.
- Hi.
你在这里
你好
- You're here!
- Hi.
你好
好的，
你好，Scotty
- Okay.
- Hi, Scotty.
你好，来这里，来这里，Scotty.
好的
- Hi. Come on. Come on, Scotty.
- Okay.
你好
- Hi.
- Hello. Hi.
你好，我是Ruby
你好，Ruby
- Hi. I'm Ruby.
- Hi, Ruby.
Hi.
你家的公园很漂亮
Your garden is so amazing.
所有的植物都有药用价值
All the plants have medicinal purposes.
药用
是的
- Medicinal.
- Yeah.
很好
That is very cool.
叹为观止
是啊
- This is incredible.
- Yeah.
他在1980年开始做这些
他只是一直在做
He started it in 1980
and he just keeps adding to it.
这是他的杰作
It's his masterpiece.
这些都是Mort建造的？
是的
- Mort built all of this?
- Yeah.
你相信这吗？
是的，我相信
- Can you believe it?
- Yes, I can.
这是我们住的地方
And this is where we live.
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
这真是太漂亮了
This is so beautiful.
我感觉像我在寺庙一样
I feel like I'm in some kind of temple.
天
我不能相信你说的
Oh, my God,
I can't believe you said that.
Calvin，她真准
什么？什么？什么？
- Calvin, she is so intuitive.
- What? What? What?
Mort 从阿米什人社区拿来的木材
祝福之意
Mort got this wood from Amish land.
It was blessed.
这些砖从一个旧的天主教会学校拿来的
And the bricks come from an old
Catholic school that was torn down.
不能想象啊
That's incredible.
楼梯，卧室
Stairway, bedroom.
这是Harry要住的地方
That's where Harry will sleep.
这是我的学习室，不要进去
This is my study. Don't go in there.
我还在整理书籍
I'm re-alphabetizing.
这是你要睡觉的地方
And this is where you'll be sleeping.
哦，这看起来像小巢
Oh, it's like a little nest.
妈妈，我们住在这里？没有门
Mom, we're in here? There are no doors.
没有人对你的事感兴趣，亲爱的
No one's interested
in your business, honey.
恩，这是浴室
Well, this is the bathroom.
我们有自己的浴室
We have our own well.
这是Mort的工作室
This is Mort's workshop!
他做了漂流木家具
He makes driftwood furniture!
Mort
Mort!
Mort，亲爱的，他们在这里
Mort, honey, they're here!
你好
Hey!
欢迎
Welcome!
他是个好孩子，好孩子
That's a good boy, good boy.
他是个很好的男孩子
所以，Ruby...
- He is such a good boy.
- So, Ruby...
你去过美术学院吗
did you go to art school?
不，我没有正式练习过
No, I didn't train formally.
我只是这学点，那学点
I just sort of picked things up
here and there.
那就是了，继续做
你会学得更多
That's right. Just do it.
You learn more that way, eh?
我意思是，看看Calvin,
I mean, look at Calvin, eh?
是的，
Right, hijo mio?
Mort，你没有喂Scotty吗？
Mort, could you not feed Scotty?
别担心，他喜欢它
我担心它的胃
- Don't worry. He loves it.
- It'll upset his stomach.
狗喜欢人类的食物，他们会做的
Dogs love human food. They do.
不，他们不会
他们会
- No, they don't.
- They do.
在我年轻的时候，我画画
I painted when I was young.
你画画
是的
- Did you?
- Yeah.
Calvin从来没有跟我说过
Calvin never told me.
他们的父亲不赞同
Well, their father didn't approve.
因为她画裸体
Because she painted porn.
各种位置
- Nudes.
- In positions.
差不多跟色情片
It was basically porn.
我觉得他们很性感，Harry.
I think they are very sexy, Harry.
Mort鼓励我再次画画
Mort's been encouraging me
to take it up again.
你应该继续，女生
你很擅长做这个
You should do it, Mama.
You're very good at it.
亲爱的。
Lovey.
- 你真是无所不能。
- 亲爱的。
- You're good at everything.
- Lovey.
做什么都这么的棒，妈妈。
Everything is so good, Mama.
- 噢，甜心。
- 棒极了。
- Oh, sweetie.
- So good.
- 好了。
- 开始了，开始了。
- Okay.
- Let's go, let's go.
还剩下一分钟，一分钟。
One minute left. One minute.
第一个词！
First word!
- 一个很短的词。
- 不，很长的词汇。
- A little word.
- No, big word.
- ‘如果’，‘它是’
-  ‘和’。
- If. It's.
- And.
- ‘它是‘。
- ‘这’，‘这’，‘这’。
- It's.
- The, the, the.
- 好吧...
- 是什么...
- Well...
- What.
- 什么。
- ‘What’.
- What?
‘What’.
什么。
What.
- 谢谢你，莫特。
- 你是我们队的。
- Thank you, Mort.
- You're on our team.
- 第2个词。
- 你是我们队的。
- Second word.
- You're on our team.
- ‘红衫’吗？
- 他们不会猜到。
- Redwoods.
- They're not gonna get it.
- 你和我，不是他们。‘我们’吗
- ‘我们’。
- You and me. Not them. Us.
- Us.
- ‘我们’...
- ‘我们’。
- We...
- Us.
一个女孩的...
A girl's...
胸部和臀部...
The T's and butt...
- 婴儿！少女？
- 噢，男孩。
- Babies! Girls?
- Oh, boy.
- ‘女人’！
- ‘女人’？
- Women!
- Women?
- ‘什么女人。’
- 莫特。
- "What women."
- Mort.
‘什么女人’
"What women."
- 倾听女人心？
- 倾听女人心。
- What Women Want?
- What Women Want.
噢，他们赢了！
Oh, they won!
- 倾听女人心？谁选的题目？
- 到这来。
- What Women Want? Who picks that?
- Come over here.
- 你太棒了。
- 莫特？他选的吗？
- You're so good.
- Mort? He picked it?
我爱你。噢，天哪。你赢的了奖品。
I love you. Oh, my God. You win the prize.
- 嗯。
- 嗯？
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- 我是她的教练。
- 但是这个违反了游戏规则。
- I'm her trainer.
- But that was against the rules!
凯文。
Calvin.
我忘了告诉你。
I forgot to tell you.
你的妈妈说她将教你怎么去烤馅饼。
Your mom said that she was gonna
teach me how to bake a pie.
她说我们可以去花园，
然后亲手摘浆果。
She says we can just go out in the garden
and pick the berries ourselves.
这很棒不是吗？
Isn't that amazing?
她以前从不像这样。
She didn't used to be like this.
不像怎么样？
Like what?
当她爸爸在她周围的时候，
她喜欢穿着球衣，并且喜欢做家务。
When Dad was around,
she wore polo shirts and cooked meat.
现在看起来她想被洗脑了一样。
It's like she's been brainwashed.
我觉得她和莫特看起来很幸福。
I think she and Mort seem really happy.
凯文？
Calvin!
- 当心！
- 快过来！
- Watch out!
- Come on!
- 快到这来！
- 嗨，凯文！
- Come down here!
- Hey, Calvin!
凯文！凯文！
Calvin! Calvin!
- 我们跳吧！
- 当心！
- Let's go!
- Watch out!
- 这水池真不错，伙计，过来。
- 棒极了！
- The water's great, man, come on.
- It's beautiful!
不，谢谢。
No, thanks.
- 噢，真不错。你错过了。
- 我答应Langdon我要读完他的书。
- Oh, it's so fun. You're missing out.
- I promised Langdon I'd finish his book.
为什么不过来陪陪我呢？
Why don't you come up here with me?
好吧，你自己玩的愉快点！
Okay, enjoy yourself!
莫特，当心点。
Mort, be careful.
小行星！
Asteroid!
耶！
Yeah!
- 耶！
- 这个真不错。
- Yeah!
- That was beautiful.
现在和我一起做，和我一起做。
Now do it with me. Do it with me.
凯文，宝贝？
Calvin, honey?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
嗯，我没事。
Yeah. I'm fine.
好吧。
Okay.
我很高兴你带她过来。
I'm really glad you brought her.
这对我很重要。
It means a lot to me.
好吧。
Okay.
晚餐在半个小时后开始。
Dinner's in a half hour.
但是，嗨，哈利，哈利，哈利。
But, hey, Harry, Harry, Harry.
- 你想不想看我的斯科特的表情？
- 想啊。
- You wanna see my impression of Scotty?
- Yeah.
这使我很开心。
That makes me laugh.
想看斯科特生气时候的表情吗？
Wanna see my impression of Scotty
when he's really angry?
想啊。
Yeah.
这太坏了。
That's so wrong.
他看起来像一个知识分子。
He's an intellectual.
噢，真不错。
Oh, that is good.
别拿斯科特开玩笑。
Don't make fun of Scotty.
噢，冷静。
Oh, calm down.
- 嘿，过来。试一下。
- 噢，天哪。你看起来真可爱。
- Hey, come on. Take it.
- Oh, my God. You look so cute here.
- 这真是经典。
- 我告诉过你我不想要它。
- That was such a classic.
- I told you I don't want it.
- 你应该去试一下，味道真不错。
- 没事的。他不需要这些。
- You should try it. It's really mellow.
- It's all right. He doesn't need it.
- 他的思想很强大。
- 是啊，不，是非常强大。
- His brain is big enough.
- Yeah, no, it's big.
如此的强大，以至于他能...
It's so big, he can...
只要运用它的思想，他就能...
他思考它：
Just with his thoughts, he can just...
He thinks it and:
- 哈利？
- 就...
- Harry?
- Just...
- 就...
- 宝贝，别待在这。
- Just...
- Honey, not here.
一个想法，我的意思是，他就能证明，嘭。
One thought. I mean, he
just can just, poof.
- 他就能，嘭。
- 哈利， 我认为你喝多了。
- He just, poof.
- Harry, I think you've had enough.
- 你现在在说什么？
- 我在说我爱你。
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about I love you.
- 什么？
- 耶，有人要去睡觉了。
- What?
- Yay, someone is ready for bed.
- 嗯，我真的要去睡觉了。
- 我们走吧。
- Yeah, I'm definitely ready.
- Let's go.
嗯，这个晚餐很不错。
Well, this was a great dinner.
- 这，让我...让我来帮助你吧。
- 你知道什么，莫特？
- Here, let me... Let me help you.
- You know what, Mort?
我认为你做的已经足够多了。
I think you've done plenty.
- 好吧，晚安。
- 好的，好的。
- Yeah. Good night.
- Great, great.
- 你还好吗？
- 嗯，你呢？
- You okay?
- Yeah, you okay?
- 走吧。
- 我很好。
- Go.
- I'm fine.
玩的愉快，各位。
Big Sur, everybody.
- 走吧，疯子。
- 我喜欢这个地方。我爱你们。
- Come on, crazy.
- I love this place. Love you.
我想我将进去和他谈谈。
I think I'm gonna go inside
and talk to him.
好吧。
Okay.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
不，没事了。
No, it's okay.
只要我知道他不是一直这样。
As long as I know
he isn't like this all the time.
他不是的。
He isn't.
好吧。
Good.
看
Look.
- 那是你吗？
- 是啊。
- Is that you?
- Yes.
那个是杰克。
And that was Jack.
他真英俊。
He's so handsome.
是的，非常非常的，
就像凯文一样。
Yes, and very, very serious,
just like Calvin.
- 他是一个高尔夫选手吗？
- 鲁比？
- He was a golfer?
- Ruby?
- 什么...？嘿。
- 鲁比，去睡觉。
- Wha...? Hey.
- Ruby, bed.
- 现在？
- 是的。
- Right now?
- Yes.
你为什么不要呢？
Why won't you take it?
我想你接受它。
I want you to have it.
- 怎么了？
- 凯文不想要我的礼物。
- What's going on?
- Calvin won't accept my present.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
- 莫特做家具做的很用心。
- 是啊。
- Mort works hard on his furniture.
- Yeah.
- 我叫它孤松椅。
- 它真漂亮。
- I call it the Lone Pine.
- That's beautiful.
- 你不喜欢吗？
- 当然，他喜欢。这是一个很棒的椅子。
- Don't you like it?
- Of course, he does. It's a great chair.
到这来，坐下，坐下。
好好感觉这个木头。
Come on, sit down, sit down.
Just feel the wood.
加尔文...
Calvin...
Skinnamarinky dinky dink
---music  “Skinny Marinky Dinky Dink, Skinny Marinky Doo”---
Dinky do
---music---
I love you
Skinnamarinky dinky dink
---music---
Dinky do
I love you
---music---
I love you in the morning
And in the afternoon
---music---
宝贝，我在读书。
Honey, I'm trying to read.
鲁比？
Ruby?
你整个周末都在读你那本无聊的书。
You read your stupid book all weekend.
你的妈妈和莫特如此的努力。
Your mom and Mort were trying so hard.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你没有任何朋友。
You don't have any friends.
我有你。
I have you.
我不需要别的其他人。
I don't need anyone else.
这是一个很大的压力。
That's a lot of pressure.
-我好寂寞。
-不要。求你不要说这些。
- I'm so lonely.
- No. Don't say that. Please.
我们该怎么办？
What do we do?
我们该如何使它变得更好？
How do we make it better?
-也许我需要上节艺术课。
-好极了。
- Maybe I could take an art class.
- Great.
一节美术课。从家里走出去。
这很好。
An art class. Get out of the house.
It's good.
我想我需要再一次花费一些夜晚在我的公寓里面。
And I think I should start spending
some nights at my apartment again.
你的公寓？
Your apartment?
一个星期一晚上。
One night a week.
作为试验。
As an experiment.
好吧。
Okay.
嗨，Scotty.到这儿来。
Hi, Scotty. Come here.
这个老师真惊人。
The teacher's just amazing.
这是一个大龄小组，
不过这里的个人水平都很高。
It's kind of an older group,
but the talent level's really high.
我想我将会学到很多。
I think I'm gonna learn a lot.
-你的夜晚怎么样？
-糟糕透了。
- How was your night?
- Terrible.
抱歉。
I'm sorry.
我不认为这个试验将要为我工作的。
I don't think this experiment
is gonna work for me.
在这关系里面肯定要留一些私人空间。
There has to be space
in the relationship.
否则，
这就像我们是一样的人了。
Otherwise,
it's like we're the same person.
听着，这是每个星期只有一个夜晚。
我觉得你可以处理它。
Listen, it's one night a week.
I think you can handle it.
我必须去洗个澡了。
I've gotta take a shower.
来吧，宝贝。
Come on, baby.
哈喽？
Hello?
-嗨。
-嗨。你在哪里？
- Hi.
- Hi. Where are you?
我们班上的人决定到外面玩，
因此我们正在酒吧里面。
A bunch of people from class
decided to go out, so we're at this bar.
你什么时候回家？
When you coming home?
我不知道。我们才刚刚到这里。
I don't know. We just got here.
我已经做过饭了。
I cooked.
抱歉，不。你知道，
我以为我们将在这里吃。
Sorry, no. You know,
I think that we're just gonna eat here.
我的意思是，我们已经好了，因此...
I mean, we already ordered, so...
那么你什么时候回家？
So when are you coming home?
我不知道。你的位置稍微有点远，
而且我们喝了点酒，因此...
I don't know. Your place is kind of far
and we're drinking, so...
你知道，我认为现在稍微有点迟了。
You know, I might be kind of late.
为什么我们不明天见面呢？
Why don't we just see each other
tomorrow?
-凯文？
-在。
- Calvin?
- Yeah.
好吧。祝你玩的愉快。
Okay. Have a great time.
凯文，我想回家。
Calvin, I wanna come home.
-不。
-我想去尿尿。
- No.
- I have to pee.
待在这。
Stay.
我现在想你了。
I miss you right now.
噢，凯文。
Oh, Calvin.
-我宁愿不讨论它
-我很抱歉。
- I'd rather not talk about it.
- I'm sorry.
我总是以为你是孤独一个人。
I always thought you walked alone.
没有人会选择孤独一生。
No man walks alone from choice.
-你要去哪里？
-去接个电话。
- Where are you going?
- To get the phone.
我能和你一起去吗？
Can I come with you?
两张7:45的票。
Two for the 7:45.
已经卖完了，9:00还有。
It's sold out. There's a 9:00.
先去散散步吧？
Take a walk first?
2张9点的票。
Two for the 9.
看这个。
Look at this.
哈喽？
Hello?
看谁回他们的电话。
Look who answered their phone.
塞勒斯，嘿。
抱歉，我最近一直很忙。
Cyrus, hey. Sorry, I've been busy.
-没关系，伙计。在忙写作？
-是啊。
- No worries, man. Busy writing?
- Yeah.
是吗？太好了，太棒了。
我一直在给他们说你正在写作。
Yeah? Good, that's great.
I keep telling them you're working on it.
出版商也越来越着急新书...
The publishers are getting anxious
about the new book...
对呢，这新书。
Right, the new book.
- 前段时间你对新书很激动...
- 我在外面呢...
- You seemed excited about it a while back...
- I'm out right now...
有什么进展没有？
我能给他们一个大概的完成时间吗...?
Any progress since then?
Can I give them some time line...?
- 塞勒斯，我过会再打给你。
-什么？
- Cyrus, I'm gonna call you back.
- What?
鲁比？
Ruby?
鲁比！
Ruby!
嘿。嘿。嘿。发生什么了？
我一转身你就不见了。
Hey. Hey, hey. What happened?
I turned around and you were gone.
- 你松开了我的手。
- 我...什么？
- You let go of my hand.
- I... What?
你松开了我的手。
You let go of my hand.
什么...？我得接个电话。
What...? I had to pick up the phone.
- 我知道，但是你放开了。
- 鲁比。
- I know, but you let go.
- Ruby.
你甚至没有注意到我不见了。
You didn't even notice I was gone.
鲁比。
Ruby.
宝贝，平静下来。
Sweetie, you have to calm down.
- 我去给你倒些水，行吗？
- 不要离开。
- I'm gonna get you some water, okay?
- No.
-不要走。
-我马上回来。
- No.
- I'll be right back.
嗨，小笨蛋
Hi, dummy.
嗨。
Hi.
他在追我...不要。
He's chasing me... No.
迈尔斯。耶。迈尔斯。
Miles. Yay, Miles.
- 谢谢。
- 他是一个水做的的宝宝。
- Thanks.
- He's a water baby.
- 我能问你一些事情吗？
- 我能帮你什么。
- Can I ask something?
- I'm coming to get you.
问吧。
Shoot.
- 要是我告诉你我又重新开始写作了，你会怎么想？
- 哦，不要，他在踢我。
- What if I told you I was writing again?
- Oh, no, he kicked me.
嘿，这很棒啊。
Hey, that's fantastic.
你准备写些什么呢？
What's it about?
重新开始写。
Writing again.
棒极了！ 喵！喵！喵！
All right! Meow! Meow! Meow!
- 噢，嗨。
- 进行的怎么样了？
- Oh. Hi.
- How's it going?
不错。
Good.
- 她还是很生气？
- 不。
- Her tits?
- No.
她只是不高兴。
She wasn't happy.
- 因此我想使她高兴起来...
- 我是皇后！
- So I made her happy...
- I'm a queen!
现在她就整天都想这样。
And now she's like this all the time.
你想问我什么呢？
如果是道德上面的？我不知道。
What are you asking me?
If it's moral? I don't know.
这显然有效。
It's obviously working.
就把它当做百解忧。
Think of it like Prozac.
- 但是你怎么知道她是不是真的快乐？
- 她是假的，明白吗？她没有真正的快乐。
- But how do I know it's real?
- It's not, okay? She's not.
她 我... 她曾经很快乐。
She I... She was.
噢，不要。
Oh, no.
- 我想让她真正的快乐起来...
- 我爱你，宝贝。
- I want to be what's making her happy...
- I love you, baby.
而不是制造成她很快乐。
Without making her happy.
那么就把鲁比写回到普通的样子。
没有什么大不了的。
So write "Ruby went back to normal."
No big deal.
我是一只小公狗，快乐的在水中游泳。
I'm a puppy dog swimming in the water.
之前我以为她会离开我。
I think she was gonna leave me before.
救命。救命。
Help. Help.
苏西曾经离开过。
Susie left once.
什么时候？为什么你没有告诉我？
When? Why didn't you tell me?
你当时很忙。
You had a lot going on.
后来她又回来了。
And she came back.
但是我仍然想着这件事。
But I still think about it.
我随时可能失去她。
I could lose her any moment.
踩到一个裂缝，
打破你妈妈的背。
Step on a crack,
break your mother's back.
我正在考虑离开几个月。
I'm thinking about going away
for a few months.
- 只有我自己。
- 你想去哪里呢？
- By myself.
- Where do you wanna go?
我不知道，一些远一点的地方。
I don't know. Somewhere far.
你可以给我寄明信片。
我非常喜欢搜信。
You could send me postcards.
I love getting mail.
或者我也可以躲在屋里面，
甚至不出门。
Or I might hole up here in the house,
not even go outside.
挺酷的。
Cool.
我们可以用枕头做一个城堡。
We could build a pillow fort.
这是你的证明自己的舞台。从你开始，米歇尔。
This is your proving
ground. Start with you, Michelle.
- 好吧。
- 你有一个优美的步伐。
- Yes.
- You have a superior walk.
- 我能在走台上看见你，但是...
- 谢谢你。
- I can see you doing runway, but...
- Thank you.
你在做什么呢？
我们准备去参加 Langdon的派对。
What are you doing?
We have's party.
- 谁？
- Langdon Tharp
- Who?
- Langdon Tharp.
- 那个作家，今天晚上是他的新书派对。
- 嘿，我正在看这个。
- The writer. His book party's tonight.
- Hey, I was watching that.
- 是啊，好几天了。
- 这就像一个马拉松。
- Yeah, for days.
- It's a marathon.
你总是让我去给我们拟定计划，我做了。
You were always asking me
to make plans for us. I did.
不要用我的话，来对付我自己。
我有权改变自己的想法。
Don't quote me to myself.
I am allowed to change my mind.
- 我不想因为这个吵架。
- 好吧，那太好了！让我们忽略它吧，然后。
- I don't want to fight about this.
- Fine, great! Let's ignore it, then.
现在看看希拉吧。
希拉看起来这么的与众不同。
Now look at Sheila.
Sheila has such a unique look.
我认为这个棒极了。
我们都可以注意到。
And I think that's wonderful.
We've all noticed it.
我们爱你的干劲。
We love your energy.
萨利的大发髻也非常的有趣...
Sally made a really interesting
choice using that big tease...
但是它太大了。
but it was too much.
她真够大胆的。
She's not afraid to be bold.
抱歉。
I'm sorry.
你最近做什么事都一上一下的，你知道吗？
Everything's been so up and down lately,
you know?
就像没有了内心的指南针。
It's like my internal compass
is just gone.
也许我应该找人谈谈。
Maybe I should talk to someone.
你过去找过人吗？
You used to see someone, didn't you?
罗森塔尔医生
Dr. Rosenthal.
也许你应该回去。
Maybe you should go back.
我想我们都正在谈论你。
I thought we were talking about you.
是啊，是啊，我们是在。
Yeah, yeah, we are.
也许你是对的。
也许我应该出去走走了。
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I just need to get out.
见一些陌生人，交一些朋友。
See people. Be social.
这个派对很有趣。
This party's gonna be fun.
Langdon. Hey, Langdon, hey.
欢迎来到我的地方。
Welcome to my cult.
- 卡尔，你应该和亚当和曼迪谈谈。
- 谁？
- Cal, you have to talk to Adam and Mandi.
- Who?
亚当和曼迪。
想买你书的版权的制作人。
Adam and Mandi. The producers
who wanna take over your option.
- 请，检查你的短信。
- 塞勒斯，这是鲁比。
- Please, check your messages.
- Cyrus, this is Ruby.
- 嗨。
- 鲁比。
- Hi.
- Ruby.
塞勒斯。
很高兴认识你。
Cyrus. Nice.
- 这是莎斯基亚
- 嗨。
- This is Saskia.
- Hi.
- 好了，走吧。
- 嗨。
- Okay. Come.
- Hi.
待在这，我马上回来。
Stay there, I'll be right back.
你想亲自来写剧本吗？
You wanna write
the screenplay yourself?
嗯，当然。是的，绝对的。
不然谁写？
Oh, of course. Yes, absolutely.
Who else would?
我不知道。我从来没有写过。
I don't know. I've never written one.
天哪，你真是一个天才，
你只要像这样完成它。
My God, you're such a genius,
you'd pick it up like that.
- 我将会告诉他那个。
- 他不喜欢这个消息的。
- I've been telling him that.
- He doesn't like that word.
你想让谁来演查理？
Who'd you wanna play Charlie?
- 我的意思是，这就是问题所在，对吧？
- 对啊。
- I mean, that's the question, right?
- Yeah.
你应该过来，和我谈谈关于它的一些事情。
You should come
and talk to me about it sometime.
现在，亚当和曼迪过来和我分享纪录片的经验。
Now, Adam and Mandi come in
with experience from documentary films.
好吧。
Yeah.
他们接触所有的东西都是真实的。
他们把他拍的很真实。
Everything they touch is authentic.
They make it real.
- 他们拍的基于现实...
- 我们对于故事也保持了真实性...
- Grounded in reality and...
- We treat narrative the exact same way...
- 你看了他们做的那个关于婴儿的纪录片了吗。
- 看了。
- You saw the baby documentary they did.
- Yes.
- 不错，棒极了。
- 使我想有个小孩。
- Okay. Genius.
- Made me wanna have a kid.
你不知道有多少的人说过了这句话。
You have no idea how many people
told us the same thing.
-不错，这很好。
- 我可以拿去看一会吗？
- Well, it's true.
- Can you hold this just for a second?
- 不，抱歉， 我要离开一会儿。
- 好吧，去吧。
- No, sorry, I'll be right back.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- 很高兴和你讲话。
- 我也是。
- Great to talk to you.
- Okay.
- 过一会在谈吧
- 好的。
- Talk to you in a bit.
- Okay.
- 待会见。 嗯，好的。
- 好的。
- See you later. Yeah, great.
- Okay.
打扰一下，抱歉。
Excuse me. Sorry.
- 卡尔。
- 莱拉。
- Cal.
- Lila.
我以为你在纽约呢。
I thought you were in New York.
没，Landgon正在帮助我出版我的小说。
No, Landgon's helping me
publish my novel.
你要出版你的小说。
You finished your novel.
我知道，这是一个很大的惊喜，这个...
你这半吊子居然写完了小说，对吗？
I know, it's a big surprise, the...
The dilettante finished something, right?
我从来没有说过这些。
I never said that.
- 你怎么样？你还在写作吗？
- 当然。
- What about you? Are you writing?
- Sure.
不错。棒极了。
Good. Great.
- 我听说你看中了某个人？
- 是啊，她在那。
- I hear you're seeing someone?
- Yeah. She's here.
打扰一下。
Excuse me.
- 她是一个作家吗？
- 不是。
- Is she a writer?
- No.
不，一个画家。
No, a painter.
棒极了。这真不坏。
That's great. It's very unthreatening.
你认为你威胁到我了吗？
You think I was threatened by you?
不，卡尔，为什么这么说？
你是一个天才。
No, Cal, why would you be?
You're a genius.
喜欢我的泳池吗？
You like my pool?
- 我们见过吗？
- 我不这样认为。
- Do I know you?
- I don't think so.
你在我的派对上做什么呢？
What are you doing at my party?
你告诉我吧。
You tell me.
你和谁一起来的？
You come with someone?
凯文 韦尔 菲尔德。
Calvin Weir-Fields.
这个天才少年。
The boy wonder.
你是一个只和女孩约会的那类作家吗？
So are you one of those girls
who only dates famous writers?
为什么？你是一个著名的作家吗？
Why? Are you a famous writer?
你可以告诉我你的名字吗？
Do you happen to have a name?
-鲁比。
- Ruby.
你是做什么的，鲁比？
And what do you do, Ruby?
没什么。
Nothing.
真新鲜的回答。
你在你的空闲时间都在做什么呢？
How refreshing.
What do you do in your spare time?
没什么。
Not much.
你知道，我一直在想，
我只是一直在思考...
You know, I was thinking,
I was just thinking...
今晚真适合游泳。
tonight would be perfect for a swim.
我没有带泳衣。
I don't have a suit.
这是一个问题吗？
Is that a problem?
没关系。我不知道为什么我会觉得
你会为我高兴。
Never mind. I don't know why
I thought maybe you'd be happy for me.
我除了支持你什么也没有做。
How was I anything but supportive?
我读了每一份草稿。
我把你放进了我的圈子。
I read every draft.
I took you into my group.
- 我把你介绍给了Langdon.
- 小气鬼。
- I introduced you to Langdon.
- Begrudgingly.
- 什么？我听不见你说什么。
- 小气鬼。
- What? I literally can't hear you.
- Begrudgingly.
你对我一点点都没有兴趣。
你从来没有。
You weren't curious about me.
You never were.
你只是对我是谁很有意见。
You just had this image of who I was.
并且无论我做什么，你都视而不见。
And anything that I did
that contradicted it, you just ignored.
什么意见？当我不出名的时候马上离开我？
What image? Where you left me
as soon as I wasn't successful?
你认为如果你出名了，我配不上你？
You think I gave a shit
if you were famous?
我想从你那里得到什么，
我不知道，我只想要你的关心。
All that I wanted was for you,
I don't know, to care about me.
关心你吗？
我的爸爸才死几个星期，你就离开了我。
Care about you?
You left weeks after my father died.
- 你想要谈论这件事吗？
- 噢，老天啊。
- Do you wanna talk about caring?
- Oh, God.
- 你知道人们怎么说你的吗？
- 你这是不可理喻。
- Do you know what people say?
- You were impenetrable.
- “你怎么会爱上这种人?”
- 我失踪去解释。
- "How'd you love that person?"
- I tried to help.
- 你拒绝我进入你的内线。
- 我只能说，“我他妈也不知道！”
- You refused to let me in.
- And I say, "I have no fucking clue!"
你唯一想交流的人，就是你自己。
The only person that you wanted to be
in a relationship with was you.
因此我让你做这些。
So I let you do that.
你真是会把自己撇的干干净净，不是吗？
You really let yourself off the hook,
don't you?
- 再见，卡尔。
- 拜拜。
- Goodbye, Cal.
- Goodbye.
祝你过得幸福。
Have a great life.
来吧。
这水温暖舒适，向我游过来吧。
Come on.
It's nice and warm. Swim to me.
你可以穿着内衣裤，如果你想的话。
You can keep your underwear on
if you like.
快过来吧。
Come on in.
- 不准偷看。
- 好吧，我发誓，我不偷看。
- No peeking.
- All right, I promise, I won't peek.
好吧。
All right.
噢，伙计。
Oh, boy.
写作是感性的，它是...
Writing is sensual. It's...
当我写作的时候，你应该看着我。
我看起来就像奥利匹斯众神。
You should see me when I write.
I'm like an Olympian.
- 噢，真的？
- 我挥舞着我的笔...
- Oh, really?
- I wield my pen...
- 你的笔？
-...就像光剑。
- Your pen?
- ...like a lightsaber.
- 你们在这里干什么？
-凯文。
- What's going on here?
- Calvin.
我们...我们就在这里泡泡澡。
We... We thought we'd take a dip.
要不要和我们一起来？
Care to join us?
- 那是什么？
- 什么是什么？
- What was that?
- What was what?
- 你知道我在说什么。
- 大惊小怪。
- You know what.
- Grow up.
斯考特
Scotty.
-嗨。
-嗨！你弄痛了我。
- Hey.
- Hey! You're hurting me.
能解释一下你刚刚在做什么。
Explain what you were doing.
你把我一个人留在了一个我完全陌生的派对。
You left me alone at a party
where I didn't know anyone.
- 我找了一个能说话的人。
- 仅仅只穿着你的内衣。
- I found someone to talk to.
- In your underwear.
以前我穿比基尼的时候，你生气过吗？
Would you have been mad
if I had been in my bikini?
你刚刚穿的不是比基尼。
You weren't wearing your bikini.
你知道看起来像什么？
Do you know what it looked like?
我的经纪人在那里，我的前女友也在那里。
My agent was there. My ex was there.
莱拉在哪里？为什么你不告诉我？
Lila was there? Why didn't you tell me?
我正忙着让你把衣服穿上。
I was too busy getting you
to put your clothes back on.
- 你应该看起来是我的女朋友
- 我就是你的女朋友。
- You're supposed to be my girlfriend.
- I am your girlfriend.
那你就表现的像一点。
So act like it.
我很抱歉没有表现的像你的理想情人。
I'm sorry I wasn't acting
like the platonic ideal of your girlfriend.
上帝啊，你这是太大惊小怪了。
Jesus, you can be such a fucking prude.
只是因为我不想你和男人们一起裸体游泳？
I don't want you skinny-dipping
with men?
因为你不什么也不让我做!
Because you don't want me
doing anything!
你有太多的规定，
并且还不告诉我它们是...
You have all these rules
and you don't tell me what they are...
直到，我打破你定的规矩。
until, whoops, I've broken one.
然后你就开始对我失望了吗？
And then you get to be disappointed
with me?
好吧，你想知道我定下的规则吗？
Okay. Do you wanna know my rules?
不要招惹其他男人。
也不要让那些男人招惹你。
Don't fuck other men.
Don't let them think about fucking you.
现在我还得对那些男人的想法负责任吗？
Now I'm responsible
for what people think?
是的，你要负责。 当你的行为，已经影响到别人的时候。
Yes, you are responsible. When you act
a certain way, it leads people on.
当你在派对上面脱了你的衣服的时候，
他们都以为你是一个荡妇。
When you take your clothes off at a party,
people think you're a slut.
因此我真的宁愿你没有做这些。
现在你清楚了吗？
So I'd really prefer if you didn't do that.
Is that clear enough for you?
檫
Fuck you!
我不是你的孩子！
I'm not your child!
你没有权利去决定我做什么。
You don't get to decide what I do.
- 要打赌吗？
- 什么？
- Wanna bet?
- What?
我相当确定我能使你做我想你做的事情。
I'm pretty sure I could make you do
whatever I want.
你想做什么呢，凯文？
把我捆绑起来？
What are you gonna do, Calvin?
Tie me up?
不。
No.
我不需要这么做。
I don't have to.
凯文...
Calvin...
我将去叫个出租车。
I'm gonna call a cab.
我们明天再谈，好吗？
Let's talk tomorrow, okay?
凯文。
Calvin.
好吧，走吧。
Fine. Go.
檫！
Fuck!
那是什么？
What was that?
你没有感觉到吗？
You didn't feel that?
那是什么？
What is that?
这他妈的是怎么回事？
What the fuck is going on?
凯文。
Calvin.
- 噢，天呐， 发生什么事情了。
- 这，看看这个。
- Oh, my God, something is happening.
- Here. Read.
这是什么？
What is this?
我的书。
My book.
这本我还没有完成的。
The one I haven't been working on.
想看看嘛？
Wanna see?
你在开玩笑吗？
Is this some sort of joke?
不，我很认真。
No. It's pretty serious.
你是在写我吗？
You're writing about me?
不，你不能写我。
这是个人隐私。
No, you can't write about me.
That's private.
我没有在写你。
I'm not writing about you.
我以前写过你。
I wrote you.
我创造了你。
I made you up.
- 什么？
- 我有一个关于一个女孩的梦。
- What?
- I had a dream about a girl.
因此你就把她写下来了。
So I wrote it down.
我给她起了个名字。
I gave her a name.
鲁比。
Ruby.
我写了所有关于她的东西，
然后有一天我醒来，她...
I wrote all kinds of things about her
and then one day I woke up and she...
你就住进了我的房子。
You were living in my house.
我能让你做任何事情...
I can make you do anything...
因为你不是真的。
because you're not real.
你病了。
You're sick.
凯文？
Calvin?
听我说。
Listen to me.
如果这是你看待他人的方式..
If this is how you think about people...
那么你将会有一个长久，孤独的人生。
then you are in for a long,
lonely fucked-up life.
你在听我说话吗？凯文？
Do you hear me? Calvin?
看，“鲁比在说法语。”
See. "Ruby speaks French."
我告诉你我能使你做任何事情。
I told you I could make you do anything.
我写。
I write it.
你做。
You do it.
Skinnamarinky dinky dink dinky do
----music---
I love you
---music---
Skinnamarinky dinky dink
Dinky do
---music---
I love you
I love you in the morning
---music---
I love you.
I'll never leave you. I love you.
---music---
I'll never leave you.
I love you. I'll never leave you.
---music---
I love your mouth. I love your nose.
I love your butt. I love your eyes.
---music---
I love your belly. I love your ears.
I love your cock. I love your nose.
I love your mouth. I love you so much.
I'll love you forever
and ever and ever and ever.
You're a genius. You're a genius.
You're a genius.
Rub...
凯文？
Calvin?
凯文。
Calvin.
你还好吗？
You okay?
她走了。
She's gone.
没事的，兄弟。
It's okay, buddy.
还行。
Okay.
没有什么帮助了。
Nothing helps.
- 什么时候是你最后一次写作，卡尔？
- 我写不出任何东西。
- When was the last time you wrote, Cal?
- I can't write.
你肯定能写。
Sure you can.
这就是你比那些心碎的笨蛋强的地方。
That's what you have over every other poor
schmuck out there with a broken heart.
你可以把它写下来。
You can write about it.
谁会去看呢？
And who would wanna read that?
很多人都会。
Lots of people.
为什么不看呢？
Why not?
你有一个相当棒的故事。
You got a pretty great story.
每个人都会认为我疯了。
Everyone will think I'm crazy.
不。
No.
他们都会认为这是虚构的。
They'll think it's fiction.
这是一个我的真实而又不可思议的爱情故事
This is the true and impossible
story of my very great love.
希望她不要看到这个故事，并且不要责备我...
In the hope that she will not read this
and reproach me...
我还留住了许多详细的细节。
I have withheld many telling details.
她的名字...
Her name...
她的生日和成长历程...
the particulars of her birth
and upbringing...
以及她的一些独有的伤疤和标记。
and any identifying scars
or birthmarks.
尽管如此，
我还是不得不为她写下这些。
All the same,
I cannot help but write this for her.
想告诉她：
To tell her:
“我对我过去写下的改变的每一个词感到抱歉”
"I'm sorry for every word
I wrote to change you."
我为很多的事情感到抱歉。
I'm sorry for so many things.
当你在的时候，我对你视而不见。
I couldn't see you when you were here.
“但是现在你走了，
我却感觉你无处不在。”
"And now that you're gone,
I see you everywhere."
“也许读到这里，会认为它是一个魔法...”
"One may read this and think it's magic..."
但是爱情本身就是一种魔法。
but falling in love
is an act of magic.
写作也是这样。
So is writing.
在《麦田的守望者》里面曾经写道：
It was once said of Catcher in the Rye:
‘小说中的奇迹又将再一次降临
'That rare miracle of fiction
has again come to pass.
一个人通过笔墨，纸张和想象力被创造出来。’
A human being has been created
out of ink, paper and the imagination.'
我不是J.D. Salinger...
I am no J.D. Salinger...
但是我亲眼见证了奇迹的诞生。
but I have witnessed a rare miracle.
任何一个作家都能体会到...
Any writer can attest...
在这个最幸运和快乐的状态...
in the luckiest, happiest state...
这些词不是出自你，
但是又是因为你出现的。
the words are not coming from you,
but through you.
是她自己找到了我。
She came to me wholly herself.
“我只是很幸运的拥有了她。”
"I was just lucky enough to be there
to catch her."
谢谢。
Thank you.
他的想象力是不是使人叹为观止？
Doesn't his imagination
just blow you away?
我的意思是，他怎么想到这些灵感的？
I mean, where does he come up
with these ideas?
- 怎么样？
- 不错
- Right?
- Yeah.
- 天才。
- 我不知道。
- Genius.
- I don't know.
我不清楚。
I don't know.
- 最近怎么样？
- 发生什么了？
- How are you?
- What's up?
故事美极了，凯文。
It's beautiful, Calvin.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的大多数的病人都不会认真对待我布置的任务。
Most of my patients don't take
my assignments this seriously.
我知道你希望在我写完这本书以后。
把她当做从未发生过的。
I know you hoped that, by writing this,
I would realize that it never happened.
只是我想象出来了她。
That I imagined her.
但是问题是...
But the thing is...
我不需要搞清楚这些。
I don't need to make sense of this.
我不在乎是否需要一个合理的解释。
I don't care
if there's no good explanation.
我希望你能够相信我，无论什么时候。
I need you to believe me anyway.
仅仅尝试一下。
Just take the leap.
至少想象一下怎么实现它。
At least imagine how it could be true.
为我。
For me.
我会试试的。
I'll work on that.
走去上厕所。
Go potty.
去上厕所。
斯科特。斯科特。
Scotty. Scotty.
斯科特
Scotty.
- 噢，嗨。
- 抱歉。
- Oh, hi.
- Sorry.
- 嗨。
- 抱歉，他是我的。
- Hi.
- Sorry, he's mine.
没事，他是友善。
It's fine. He's so friendly.
- 他的名字是什么？
- 斯科特。
- What's his name?
- Scotty.
斯科特。这真有趣，这...
Scotty. That's funny, that's...
这个狗和书里面的同名。
That's the name of the dog in this book.
你读了它吗？
Have you read it?
你喜欢吗？
Did you like it?
抱歉。你刚刚说了什么吗？
Sorry. Did you say something?
是啊，我只是问了你喜不喜欢这本书。
Yeah, I just asked if you liked it.
你觉得怎么样？
What do you think?
借我我书的朋友认为这本书有一点点自负...
My friend who lent it to me thought
it was kind of pretentious...
但是我真的很喜欢它。
but I really like it so far.
我们以前见过吗？
Have we met before?
我不知道。
I don't know.
你看起来很眼熟。
You seem really familiar.
也许在别的地方我们互相认识了。
Maybe we knew each other
in another life.
或者也许我们只是在别的咖啡厅见过。
Or maybe we just go
to the same coffee shop.
你在做什么
除了和你的狗散步之外？
What do you do
besides go for walks with your dog?
我是一个作家。
I'm a writer.
你写些什么？
What do you write?
难怪为什么你看起来这么眼熟。
So that's why you look so familiar.
也许。
Maybe.
我的朋友说你的书很自负是我看的玩笑。
I was kidding about
my friend calling it pretentious.
没事。
It's okay.
我们能重新开始吗？
Can we start over?
好啊。
Yes.
- 我可以坐下吗？
- 嗯，请。
- May I sit down?
- Oh, please.
别告诉我结局好吗？
Just don't tell me how it ends, okay?
保证。
Promise.